

# **HUFAID BIN SAEED**

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

+92-312-3088445 hufaidk@gmail.com

# **PROFILE INFO**

I'm a multi-skilled professional with 3+ years of experience in WordPress development, technical support, customer care, and virtual assistance. I can develop custom themes, troubleshoot technical issues, provide excellent customer service, and handle administrative tasks efficiently. I have strong communication and problem-solving skills and a passion for delivering quality results.

English \_\_\_\_\_

Urdu

# WORK EXPERIENCE

#### **2018 - Present**

Wordpress Developer

Freelance

Build various websites for various Businesses, Non-Profits orgs and LMS.

Experienced in Building Ecommerece Stores.

## 2020 - Present

**Technical Support** 

Freelance

Have worked for various international firms/companies as customer support representative.

#### 2018- Present

Social Media

Management/Marketing

Freelance

Building and managing the branded social media accounts for Facebook, Twitter, LinkedIn, and Google Plus, driving a consistent increase in traffic across all platforms

## **EDUCATION**

# **Bachelor Of Software Engineering**

2018 - 2022 Sarhad University of Science & Technology

### MY SKILLS

- Web Design
- Wordpress
- JavaScript (ReactJS)
- Virtual Assistance
- Customer Support
- Marketing

#### REFERENCE

Will be provided upon request